[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following groups of animals does nematology study?", "correct_answer": "Roundworms", "incorrect_answers": ["All worms", "Tapeworms", "Intestinal parasites"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens if you play all of your letters during the game of Scrabble?  \n(Note:  This would not include the end of the game when your rack is not full)", "correct_answer": "You get an extra 50 points", "incorrect_answers": ["Your opponent(s) lose(s) a turn", "You win", "You are penalized 25 points"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1987 Larroquette starred in a broad comedy that featured Kim Bassinger, Bruce Willis, William Daniels, Phil Hartman,and Joyce Van Patten. What was the name of this movie ?", "correct_answer": "Blind Date", "incorrect_answers": ["A Certain Stranger", "Kissing the Stranger", "The One"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fresh, green vegetable comes from India, where people have been growing it for 3000 years. Although we regard it as a vegetable, it is actually a fruit and reproduces by seeds.", "correct_answer": "Cucumber", "incorrect_answers": ["Asparagus", "Pepper", "Tomato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When magma cools and becomes solid below Earths surface, the resultant rocks are called Plutonic, but when when magma reaches the surface and crystallizes there, formed rocks are called this.", "correct_answer": "Volcanic", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercuric", "Surfaced", "Veneric"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An elephants brain is half the size of the human brain.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of all of the Postulates of Euclid, one stood out as a big sticking point. To this day it involves such things as space travel, physics, and triangles. Which postulate was it?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "3", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Odd-numbered dress sizes are usually for younger women.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What catchy tagline was used for the theatrical poster of the 1962 movie Lolita, directed by Stanley Kubrick?", "correct_answer": "How did they ever make a movie of Lolita?", "incorrect_answers": ["What on earth were they thinking?", "Most scandalous film of all time", "She was only a child. Until..."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which mini country was among the European Union founding members?", "correct_answer": "Luxembourg", "incorrect_answers": ["Malta", "Monaco", "Liechtenstien"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The second Another Cinderella Story music video starts with this character relaxing on a bus bench.", "correct_answer": "Joey", "incorrect_answers": ["Dustin", "Britt", "Natalia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Denzel Washington born?", "correct_answer": "December 28, 1954", "incorrect_answers": ["September 24, 1952", "December 15, 1956", "March 7, 1958"]}]